oh boy uh hello everybody Welcome Back
to another episode of hermitcraft but uh
I I've started recording in a bit of a
rush because I literally logged on and I
only set up my flag yesterday and it's
already gone false and dark literally
were here seconds ago hours ago I don't
know they were literally just here and
it's gone look I said hey you've got it
already and they were like I literally I
literally had just finished it and I
logged back on and it was gone and they
were like I was like did you at least
die and they just said no definitely not
so they must have died and they said not
even one come on how many lives did you
lose and was it worth it and they said
we got a flag it was worth it
and here's the funny thing so they went
through this they must have died I don't
know how many times they must have died
at least a couple of times but here's
the really funny thing so they've been
in the base right
but they didn't see this is girl hasn't
actually finished protecting his flag
yet they will be but he will be by the
time that this video comes out don't
worry but his flag was right here the
whole time and like it was it wasn't
even covered up so they must have just
like not seen this bit to be fair this
part is actually behind the aquarium and
unless you were looking directly at it
or went round the back here you
definitely wouldn't see it but come on
so at least I got a few lies off of them
how many I don't know yet but oh my
goodness we're down a flag and we have
zero we have zero of their Flags so I
think maybe it's time to do a little
Skirmish of our own and try and get one
of their Flags but I'm gonna need to
prepare for that first in a respawny
kind of way and I'm also gonna need to
get some help so I'm gonna have to
choose a team member to join me on this
little Skirmish the only person lesson
that I could get to do this Skirmish
with me was molbo gumbo himself
aim is still going on I can't help but
notice that you are
a lot more geared up than me I'm so
ready wait wait uh where's your outfit
yeah well this is what I'm talking I'm
in a tailored suit like a nice tailored
suit isn't that how James Bond does it
anyway that's true
here's the debrief we're going in for
the flag hopefully you know somewhat
away around their base and I've got a
shulker box full of gear in case we die
lots and I've got a couple of beds so we
can set our spawn there so we can keep
going in until we get a flag okay that
sounds good uh should we I mean it is
dark right now so should we probably
make our way over there now let's head
over right now let's get get some gear
on because it's actually not it's not
too safe out there right now all right
let's let's charge on over I've got
stuck on the door instantly you know
what like are you sure you want to bring
me along no no
oh come here come and come over here
quickly just uh go run in here and click
the the button there what does that what
what's that gonna do
oh hello yeah yeah right there's all the
Guardians that I I placed there oh my
goodness oh no my own Guardians okay so
you're where are you you're over there I
can't even get how do you get this moat
has defeated me dude I'm defeated this
is not how I imagine this is not going
well
there's a guardian wrecking my face
right now hold on I've got um got a
solution this is oh I've created their
own I've created their own defenses
actually awful I don't like this dude
where's the bed I'm going for it because
it's becoming daylight we can't set our
spawn yet okay wait could you I'm okay
I'm gonna block across I'm gonna block
across yep quickly
look at how many mobs there are oh this
is the worst infiltration place the bed
where's the bed
job go okay
did you get it so have you set your
spawn yeah undercover yeah under cover
of Nightfall we took so long but it's
now dead it's now Daybreak
we are so useless and I'm using the
plural for once I'm using the plural
because thank you you were just as bad
as me oh right here oh yeah you're
literally oh yeah
um so you want to rock paper scissors
for this
okay
um so if you want oh I don't I just have
said that should we just should I just
open it yeah
yeah easy oh easy peasy not a problem
did you just did you just kill that
Phantom it was gonna hit dude there is
more than enough to worry about
oh okay I just hit you wait wait
oh my God there's a blaze there dude
that's me
um yeah I think this might let's get out
of here I've got a bailing a bailing so
fast
shut the door okay right let's regroup
out here yes so I'm not even sure what
just happened I'll briefly open the door
again okay there's there's a lot of
phantoms yeah you're worried about the
killing one Phantom there's so many in
there I I think without these potions we
would have been dead yeah I think we
actually got but I had said they seem to
be wearing out I don't know yeah I've
only got strength yeah all right let's
yeah let's get out
wait hang on hang on
well they're just chilling there at the
minute they don't seem to be that
bothered with us at the moment no no oh
no that one problem with you watch out
dude
can we just go go down yeah let's just
go down I'm not sure where this fella
came from I thought I would definitely I
genuinely thought that was you
all right oh okay okay okay okay
these are a problem these are a problem
okay well I'm dead I'm so dead
uh now I'm allowed to break oh no okay
so you've died
don't worry I'm coming back your stuff
went everywhere dude
uh I think I think it's best that we
just we just run run the Labyrinth we've
got speed run the Labyrinth okay okay
okay yeah right that's the two dodging
these Phantoms is not possible I uh oh
wow this is like you know when like that
sort of that painting with all the
staircases yeah it's like it's like
that's like being inside where are you
I've lost you I was trying to follow you
but I've genuinely lost where you were
going I found something I found
something okay so I can see one of their
Flags no way
that was dude
genius
um they're still am I allowed to go
through here I mean yeah yeah yeah
there's still Phantoms here I've I've
got
do we just go in oh oh no oh that made
me jump oh that made me jump so much
dude oh oh there is so much lava
lava I just suffocated no I I died in
lava I've lost I've lost all the stuff
that I had which wasn't very much but uh
I had I had I had all my food on me more
importantly so I'm gonna have to grab
some of that
oh great great fantastic yeah I'm the
type of man that brings raw fish to a
skirmish uh we've lost two lives now ah
three
three no three lives three no eight
yeah three lives because you died and
then we both died
okay okay so let's try and not lose any
more lives as a matter of urgency so
maybe we should take care of these guys
because these yeah the Panthers need to
go they've got to go that you know what
they're they're so much less frightening
when they don't scream that's true
actually yeah they're just wondering why
they were kind of just a little bit more
yeah they're just silenced let's keep
running I don't remember where okay
marked where the flags are because that
that's got a banner above it I don't
know oh okay I just got hit by the
Phantom okay we need to make our way
down potatoes my potatoes are here
you found your potato I found my
potatoes all is well in the world uh
okay should we should we convene down
here
yeah I'm making my way down to where the
banner was I remember where it was oh
okay
this maze is actually so well made I
it's so I'm struggling so much it is
very impressive now I'm kind of
wondering how do we disable the the Trap
that they
made and what was it did it just piston
us
how about this what I'll do is I'll run
in and run out and we'll see what
happens is it a puffer fish detector
so how do we get through it
do we just break the blocks
oh it do I mean dude that Redstone it's
the Redstone it's that Redstone oh it's
an old school one it's got to be right
so oh yes okay watch out for that lava
do we just break it or is there another
way in perhaps I mean okay so that that
Redstone is no longer updated do not
walk over that Redstone what if I okay
if I give the thing fish what if I give
it fish
but
I thought if I fed it fish it might open
for us maybe no I mean do we need ender
pearls to get through this oh dude
they're in my box upstairs okay you know
what I'm going I'm going for it I'll be
back okay stay there I'll be back in two
seconds made it okay okay am I going in
are you going in I've only got three
ender pearls so we can either do two in
and one out or just one in one out one
in one out I think okay I know it's
gonna be you because you're the one with
the effective effective costume so if
you so dodge dodge the Redstone make
sure you don't touch that
please don't kill me kill me
you seem like you're doing okay
okay
we we did it we have a flag
well not yet we need to get back to the
base
okay we haven't captured it we've we've
got it uh oh yeah getting out is an
absolute nightmare why did you not
remember how you got out man because
it's so dude this whole thing looks the
same
it's true
uh oh oh dude are you all right was that
you
know it was
I'm not to blame them
have under Pals we could totally just
end up I you have you have the only one
left ah okay yeah and that could have
been a very risky move dude yes we might
have made it let's go and grab our
shulker box and get out of here Pronto
well under the cover of daylight we
managed away
instead it seems like headquarters but
unfortunately we lost three lives
oh yeah that's a good point that's quite
a significant amount of lives once once
a flag is captured a flag is captured
that's it you can't oh really yeah
because otherwise the wall would never
end that's very true so yeah at the
moment we're three down each so yeah and
they've already secured the flag that I
built protection for yeah okay
yeah we're now even and we're in I think
we can get this to the meeting room and
it will be officially captured well I'm
trapped bits I'm glad that I was
actually of some assistance dude I
finally wouldn't have thoughts I mean
those are those are they're legal aren't
they they are a legal thing to use okay
okay well how else were you meant to get
through there it's very true just before
people light us up down in the comment
section that is a totally legal maneuver
we're totally we're in the right we got
we got our first flag
this is a fake flag this is a real one
this has got to be yeah no it's not real
it's good I can see the mark of
genuineness on the back it's got the
bags yeah signed by all the team Star
members it'll be on eBay yeah yeah
okay
all right sweet dude we nailed it
excellent all right so now it's just
time to protect our other flags and send
in some more people to get the others
well that was actually pretty successful
we can actually just leave this Banner
here we don't have to do anything
because we've all agreed to just leave
the flags where they are once they've
been captured so we can we can show them
off as much as we like so there's not a
lot for me to do inside the G team base
at this moment in time I guess I can
just check on things downstairs because
people have been working on other things
while I have been doing my Skirmish and
stuff so my flag is now officially gone
we now have to just make sure that iskal
is all prepared with his defense and
then I guess it stresses as well once
that's done yep still uh it's actually
protected this time it's actually got
the glass behind it so they can see
where it is but they've got to work out
how to get in here I actually have no
idea what is really done here something
to do with Vault Keys it sounds a bit
complicated you should have just put
lava everywhere like I did
I think I'm just gonna leave everything
where it is and see how this plays out
because I've got a lot of other things
to do because I want to start easing
into working back on my base for a
little while whoa this has changed
what's going on here there's like a
Spectators chair giant chair hold on
that looks like con yeah so concorp is
behind this they've got a map a couple
of chairs so they can watch the whole
thing that's pretty funny and yeah we
are actually one life lower than them
for some reason I guess someone on the G
team lost their life to a trap but
seeing as two out of the Six Flags are
captured it means that the war one way
or another is going to be coming to an
end fairly shortly so I want to start
easing back into things in my base and
there's uh it's just in this annoying
state of nearly finishedness so this is
my base if everyone has forgotten we've
spent so much time on the G team base
that I've really not been here very much
there's lots of things that just aren't
done I haven't connected up this giant
ring to the floor which I think would
actually make this it would make it look
way more complete but at the same time
it's nice being able to see all of the
sea and I also need to finish putting
everything in these things I want to
finish up there I want to make that look
way more green than it is I need to come
up with something to put in there and I
need to finish what I'm doing in here as
well because this is where I was going
to store all of my stuff and something
that I talked about for about every
episode since I made these towers is a
giant mob farm within here because
actually this is a fantastic place for
mobs to spawn
so I basically need to figure out if
there's a way to make an automatic mob
farm with the layers that I've got but
as you can see it's a bit of a mess in
here I have to clean most of this out
but I'm pretty sure I can see if it's
even possible first there's got to be a
way of dispensing water to clear out the
platforms one at a time even if I have
to square these off in some way it must
be possible and efficiency it really
isn't much of an issue I just need to
produce some things I can't believe this
I haven't actually
there's so many things unfinished about
this base look at this most of this is
still concrete powder how has this gone
on for so long well I've only I was only
up there for about two seconds and
stuff's already spawning so we know that
this is this is gonna work it's just
about how I push these guys off of the
platform I think because this is such an
awkward shape if I put some water here
basically it's just gonna push the mobs
like in Corners like this so I've got to
come up with like an optimal shape and
then just roll with it no matter how
efficient or unefficient it is maybe I
should get the opinion of somebody who
knows how to make these farms and maybe
I shouldn't just guess how to make this
because I haven't made a mob farm
suitable for this version in Minecraft
ever yeah ever the the only way I know
how to make mob Farms is to just create
platforms and let them walk off the edge
and I don't think that's how it works
anymore so I think we've got to I think
we've got to get like a second opinion
on this because I'm a little bit just a
little bit out of my depth here oh hold
on what's this thank you for all the
stone and the help with the buttons oh
that was from iskau
basically he's giving me a beacon and an
egg
now why is he giving me an egg I've got
nothing to do with eggs
basically he was making a Wither Skull
farm and I donated several shulker boxes
full of stone and I helped him place all
the buttons for his farm maybe iska
would be the one to help me with it
since I helped him with his farm maybe
he could help me with with mine but
another thing that I want to do is why
I've got some cyan terracotta is you see
that these sort of Stripes go outwards
I'm thinking I need to add one on this
bit but I've been struggling to work out
which direction I don't know if I want
them to go outwards as well so they all
emanate or maybe I reverse it and have
it go downwards or this way upwards
towards it so it kind of yeah so it kind
of I don't know I really don't know I
could I guess I could just try some see
how it works I think we just match
what's going on here we go from here and
up and out
that's really good that I've got a
beacon because I've literally only got
the one in the base and I really could
use one to be honest with you I really
could
and done let's see if this example works
in the grand scheme of things
you know what that doesn't look right or
maybe it's just because I'm so used to
it or maybe it needs another stripe
but something about it doesn't look
I mean it's exactly the same pattern
it's four four tall goes down in
increments of three it should in theory
be the same or maybe I just need to
change my angle
um
I guess it works maybe I just need
another one up here somewhere or maybe
it's the distance here because this is
five blocks and that is only two because
otherwise I wouldn't have worked as well
hmm
I'll finish it and if I decide that I
don't like it then I'll just put it back
later Mumbo is AFK again on the server
somewhere
I wonder what he's up to
it turns out that Mumbo is a proper
messy pup and didn't get rid of our
signs so maybe we can do a bit of a
drive-by on most of these and
it
take about
nice
die
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
okay just go in a bit more gently there
we go
it's yeah it's gonna take a look I can
see why he didn't do this because it's
gonna take a little while to get all of
this cleared up ah well that one's just
gonna fall
yeah this is actually a lot more work
than I thought because landing on one
block is extraordinarily tough because
even if you get it bang on you most of
the time just fall straight off
oh no
that's why I keep emergency Electro with
me at all times
my stuff is probably going to be
everywhere look there's not that much
left
where is it where's my oh here it is
it's not even not even made its way to
the top yet
and one more left oh this has been a
really really dull cleanup I'm not gonna
lie there we go sorted I'm sure Mumbo
will be thankful for that now I have
talked previously about the rail station
that's going to be here but I honestly
need to find out what the plans are for
this island if there even are plans for
this island maybe we could use it or
maybe we could destroy it we'll have to
find out but that's all that I have time
for today everybody thank you very much
for watching I hope you enjoyed our
little Skirmish and I want to know what
your thoughts are about the war and how
it's all going down but I'm afraid
that's all I have time for today I
really do want to get back into this but
a lot of it is gonna have to be off
camera because working on my base it
really isn't the most exciting thing but
on the other hand it really does need to
get finished so I might do a time lapse
connecting this up I might even finish
Bikini Bottom at some point because
we've got Squidward's house we've got
SpongeBob's house but where's Patrick's
house
where is Patrick's house so thank you
very much everyone for watching I hope
you've enjoyed this episode I hope you
enjoyed mine and mumbo's little Skirmish
and let me know what you guys think can
you believe that if you if you include
all of the episodes in the lead up to
the war the Civil War has been about 20
episodes on this channel which is
absolute Madness so it'll be nice to
have a bit of a change of scene after
all of this is done but we've got to
secure the win for the G team because
after all
we are the best where did I go oh well
goodbye